A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, International Relations, RG 1.3, Series 155 FA388A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Relations, 1971-1989; 155
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XXX): "World Press Reception of the WOCOL Final Report", India-Netherlands, 1980 June (Box 74, Folder 822)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology: World Coal Study: Supplementary Material (XXXI): "World Press Reception of the WOCOL Final Report", Poland-United States, 1980 June (Box 74, Folder 823)
  - Middle East Peace Meetings, 1983-1985 (Box 74, Folder 824)
  - Mohonk Preserve, Inc.: Middle East Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 825)
  - Mohonk Preserve, Inc.: Middle East Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 75, Folder 826)
  - Mohonk Preserve, Inc.: Middle East Conference, 1986-1989 (Box 75, Folder 827)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology, 1980 April (Box 75, Folder 828)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology, 1980 May-December (Box 75, Folder 829)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology, 1981-1982 (Box 75, Folder 830)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology, 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 831)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology: Supplementary Material (I): Background Documents I-II (for Assessment of Renewable Energy Technologies docket conference, June 2, 1980), 1980 May 27 (Box 75, Folder 832)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology: Supplementary Material (II): Background Document III (for Assessment of Renewable Energy Technologies docket conference, June 2, 1980), 1980 May 27 (Box 75, Folder 833)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology: Supplementary Material (III): Related Document I (for Assessment of Renewable Energy Technologies docket conference, June 2, 1980), 1980 May 27 (Box 76, Folder 834)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology: Supplementary Material (IV): Related Document II (for Assessment of Renewable Energy Technologies docket conference, June 2, 1980) (Box 76, Folder 835)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology: Supplementary Material (V): Related Documents III-IV (for Assessment of Renewable Energy Technologies docket conference, June 2, 1980), 1980 May 27 (Box 76, Folder 836)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology: Supplementary Material (VI), 1981-1982 (Box 76, Folder 837)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology: Supplementary Material (VII): Workshop on "U. S. Participation in International Science and Technology Cooperation", September 28-29, 1983, 1983 September (Box 76, Folder 838)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Renewable Energy Technology: Supplementary Material (VIII): Workshop on "U. S. Participation in International Science and Technology Cooperation", September 28-29, 1983, 1983 September (Box 76, Folder 839)
  - (489) – National Medical and Dental Association (NAMDA): Primary Health Care, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 840)
  - (489) – National Medical and Dental Association (NAMDA): Primary Health Care, 1985-1989 (Box 76, Folder 841)
  - National Planning Association: Export Development, 1979 March-June (Box 76, Folder 842)
  - National Planning Association: Export Development, 1979 July-1980 (Box 76, Folder 843)
  - National Planning Association: Export Development, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 76, Folder 844)
  - National Planning Association: Export Development: Supplementary Material, 1980, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 845)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council: Energy Conference, 1981 May-June (Box 76, Folder 846)
  - Natural Resources Defense Council: Energy Conference, 1981 July-1982 (Box 77, Folder 847)
  - Nigerian-American Relations: Conference, 1979-1984 (Box 77, Folder 848)
  - Simon Robert Nkonoki, 1979-1980 (Box 77, Folder 849)
  - Simon Robert Nkonoki, 1980-1981 (Box 77, Folder 850)
  - Øystein Noreng, 1980-1983 (Box 77, Folder 851)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities: Energy Analysis, 1976-1979 (Box 77, Folder 852)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities: Energy Analysis: Evaluation, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 853)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities: Energy Analysis: Supplementary Material (I): "Analysis of Selected Global Energy Models", 1979 January 30 (Box 77, Folder 854)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities: Energy Analysis: Supplementary Material (II): "The IEA Energy Simulation Model", 1976 January (Box 78, Folder 855)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities: Energy Analysis: Supplementary Material (III): "An Acceptable Future Nuclear Energy System", 1977 December (Box 78, Folder 856)
  - Michel Oksenberg, 1981-1987 (Box 78, Folder 857)
  - Overseas Development Council: Chandra Singh Hardy, 1979-1982 (Box 78, Folder 858)
  - Overseas Development Council: Chandra Singh Hardy: Supplementary Materials: Working Papers Nos. 1, 5, 7, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 859)
  - Overseas Development Council: North/South Negotiations, 1981-1984 (Box 78, Folder 860)
  - Overseas Development Council: North/South Negotiations: Supplementary Material (I), 1981 (Box 78, Folder 861)
  - Overseas Development Council: North/South Negotiations: Supplementary Material (II), 1981 (Box 79, Folder 862)
  - Overseas Development Council: North/South Negotiations: Supplementary Material (III), 1982 (Box 79, Folder 863)
  - Overseas Development Institute: Labor Conditions and Industrialization, 1983-1987 (Box 79, Folder 864)
  - Overseas Development Institute: Labor Conditions and Industrialization: Supplementary Material (I): Annual Report 1982 (Box 79, Folder 865)
  - Overseas Development Institute: Labor Conditions and Industrialization: Supplementary Material (II): "South Asia's Exports to the EEC - Obstacles and Opportunities", 1979 (Box 79, Folder 866)
  - Overseas Development Institute: Labor Conditions and Industrialization: Supplementary Material (III): "Adjustment and Financing in the Developing World: The Role of the International Monetary Fund", 1982 (Box 79, Folder 867)
  - Oxford University: Rajeshwar Dayal, 1975-1983 (Box 79, Folder 868)
  - Oxford University: Rajeshwar Dayal: Evaluation, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 869)
  - Pacific Community: Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 80, Folder 870)
  - Pan Pacific Community Association, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 80, Folder 871)
  - Pan Pacific Community Association, Inc., 1982 January-August (Box 80, Folder 872)
  - Pan Pacific Community Association, Inc., 1982-1984 (Box 80, Folder 873)
  - Pan Pacific Community Association, Inc.: Workshops, 1983-1984 (Box 80, Folder 874)
  - Pan Pacific Community Association, Inc.: Workshops, 1984-1985 (Box 80, Folder 875)
  - Partnership for African Development, 1982 January-March (Box 81, Folder 876)
  - Partnership for African Development, 1982 April-October (Box 81, Folder 877)
  - Partnership for African Development, 1982 November-December (Box 81, Folder 878)
  - Partnership for African Development, 1983-1985 (Box 81, Folder 879)
  - Partnership for African Development: Supplementary Material: "Lessons Learned from the Experience of ADELA, CDC and SIFIDA", 1985 June (Box 81, Folder 880)
  - Peace Corps Institute, 1981-1982 (Box 81, Folder 881)
  - Peace Corps Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 82, Folder 882)
  - Peace Corps Institute: Conference, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 883)
  - Peace Corps Institute: Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 884)
  - Peace Through Law Education Fund: U.S.-Soviet Relations Congressional Conference, 1983-1984 (Box 82, Folder 885)
  - Princeton University: International Monetary System, 1982-1987, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 886)
  - Princeton University: Kampuchea Publication, 1982-1985 (Box 82, Folder 887)
  - Sanford C. Reback, 1981-1982 (Box 82, Folder 888)
  - Renewable Energy Technology, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 889)
  - Resources for the Future: Hyderabad Fuelwood Market, 1979-1983 (Box 83, Folder 890)
  - Resources for the Future: Hyderabad Fuelwood Market: Final Report - "Fuelwood Survey of Hyderabad", 1983 September (Box 83, Folder 891)
  - Resources for the Future: Hyderabad Fuelwood Market: Financial Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 83, Folder 892)
  - Resources for the Future: Hyderabad Fuelwood Market: Supplementary Material: "Fuelwood in Urban Markets", 1984-1985 (Box 83, Folder 893)
  - Resources for the Future: Energy Analysis, 1977-1980 (Box 83, Folder 894)
  - Resources for the Future: Energy Analysis: Evaluation, 1978 (Box 83, Folder 895)
  - Resources for the Future: Energy Analysis: Supplementary Material: "Caught Unawares: The Energy Decade in Retrospect" by Martin Greenberger, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 896)
  - Resources for the Future: World Energy Problems, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 897)
  - Resources for the Future: World Energy Problems, 1978-1979 (Box 84, Folder 898)
  - Resources for the Future: World Energy Problems, 1984 January-February (Box 84, Folder 899)
  - Resources for the Future: World Energy Problems: Evaluation, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 900)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Alastair Buchan, 1974, 1977, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 901)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Alastair Buchan, 1974-1976 (Box 84, Folder 902)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Alastair Buchan, 1977, 1981-1983 (Box 84, Folder 903)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Alastair Buchan: Evaluation, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 904)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Chinese Policies, 1974-1975, 1977, 1983-1984 (Box 84, Folder 905)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Chinese Policies, 1974-1977, 1979-1980, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 906)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Chinese Policies: Supplementary Material (I): "The Origins of the Cultural Revolution, 1: Contradictions Among the People 1956-1957", by Roger MacFarquhar, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 907)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Chinese Policies: Supplementary Material (II): "The Origins of the Cultural Revolution, 2: The Great Leap Forward 1958-1960", by Roger MacFarquhar, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 908)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Front of File, 1977-1984 (Box 85, Folder 909)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Front of File, 1977-1979 (Box 85, Folder 910)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy, 1977 March-August (Box 85, Folder 911)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy, 1977 September-December (Box 85, Folder 912)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy, 1978 January-March (Box 86, Folder 913)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy, 1978 April-July (Box 86, Folder 914)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy, 1978 August-December (Box 86, Folder 915)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy, 1979 January-July (Box 86, Folder 916)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy, 1979 August-1980 March (Box 86, Folder 917)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy, 1980 April-1981 March (Box 86, Folder 918)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy, 1981 April-December (Box 86, Folder 919)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy, 1982 January-1983 June (Box 86, Folder 920)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Evaluation, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 921)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (I): "World Nuclear Energy", edited by Ian Smart, 1982; Additional copy in Library: 333.79 WOR (Box 87, Folder 922)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (II): Annual Reports, 1973-1979 (Box 87, Folder 923)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (III): Working Papers, International Consultative Group on Nuclear Energy, 1978 November (Box 87, Folder 924)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (IV): Working Papers, International Consultative Group on Nuclear Energy, 1979 September (Box 87, Folder 925)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (V): Working Papers, International Consultative Group on Nuclear Energy, 1979 (Box 87, Folder 926)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (VI): Working Papers, International Consultative Group on Nuclear Energy, 1979, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 927)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (VII): National Notes on Public Acceptance, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 928)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (VIII): Clippings Related to International Consultative Group on Nuclear Energy (ICGNE) Studies, 1980 (Box 88, Folder 929)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (IX): "Nuclear Power Struggles", by William Walker and Måns Lönnroth, pp. 1-90, 1982 July (Box 88, Folder 930)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (X): "Nuclear Power Struggles", by William Walker and Måns Lönnroth, pp. 91-195, 1982 July (Box 88, Folder 931)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (XI): "Nuclear Power Struggles", by William Walker and Måns Lönnroth, pp. 196-296, 1982 July (Box 88, Folder 932)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (XII): "Future U. S.-Japanese Nuclear Energy Relations", 1979 October (Box 88, Folder 933)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (XIII): Rockefeller Foundation Working Paper - "International Energy Supply: A Perspective from the Industrial World", 1978 March (Box 88, Folder 934)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (XIV): "Report of the International Consultative Group on Nuclear Energy", 1980 January 17 (Box 88, Folder 935)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (XV): International Consultative Group on Nuclear Energy (ICGNE), Initial Meeting, Chatham House, October 31-November 2, 1977, 1977 October 31-November 2 (Box 88, Folder 936)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (XVI): International Consultative Group on Nuclear Energy, ICGNE II, Chatham House, London, May 15-17, 1978, 1978 May 15-17 (Box 89, Folder 937)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (XVII): International Consultative Group on Nuclear Energy, ICGNE III, Le Mirador, Vevey, Switzerland, September 27-29, 1978, 1978 September 27-29 (Box 89, Folder 938)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (XVIII): International Consultative Group on Nuclear Energy, ICGNE IV, Hotel Melia Don Pepe, Marbella, Spain, January 10-12, 1979, 1979 January 10-12 (Box 89, Folder 939)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (XIX): International Consultative Group on Nuclear Energy, ICGNE V, Villa Serbelloni, Bellagio, Italy, May 1-4, 1979, 1979 April-May (Box 89, Folder 940)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Southern Africa Conflict: Front of File, 1979, 1981, 1983-1984 (Box 89, Folder 941)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Southern Africa Conflict, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 942)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Southern Africa Conflict, 1979-1982 (Box 89, Folder 943)
  - Royal Institute of International Affairs: Southern Africa Conflict: Supplementary Material, 1978-1979 (Box 89, Folder 944)
  - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies: Eastern European Fellows, 1981-1987 (Box 90, Folder 945)
  - Scientists' Institute for Public Information: Security Conference, 1982-1984 (Box 90, Folder 946)
  - Secretariat for Futures Studies: European Oil Symposium, 1978-1981, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 947)
  - Secretariat for Futures Studies: European Oil Symposium: Supplementary Material, 1979, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 948)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific: Front of File and Evaluation, 1980, 1983, 1986-1987 (Box 90, Folder 949)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific, 1979-1985 (Box 90, Folder 950)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific: Supplementary Material (I): SeCAP Workshop on "Reducing Nuclear Threats in Asia", April 13-15, 1984, San Diego, California: Research Papers for the First Workshop Session, 1984 April (Box 90, Folder 951)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific: Supplementary Material (II): SeCAP Workshop on "Reducing Nuclear Threats in Asia", April 13-15, 1984, San Diego, California: Research Papers for the Third Workshop Session, 1984 April (Box 90, Folder 952)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific: Supplementary Material (III): SeCAP Workshop on "Reducing Nuclear Threats in Asia", April 13-15, 1984, San Diego, California: Research Papers for the Second, Fourth and Fifth Workshop Sessions, 1984 April (Box 91, Folder 953)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific: Supplementary Material (IV): "The U. S.-Japan Relationship in the 1980s", 1983 January (Box 91, Folder 954)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific: Supplementary Material (V): Workshop on "The Soviet Challenge: Potential Crises in the Persian Gulf and East Asia", Volume I, Drafts of Papers Presented, 1980 September (Box 91, Folder 955)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific: Supplementary Material (VI): Workshop on "The Soviet Challenge: Potential Crises in the Persian Gulf and East Asia", Volume II, Background Papers, 1980 September (Box 91, Folder 956)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific: Supplementary Material (VII): Workshop on "The Soviet Challenge: Potential Crises in the Persian Gulf and East Asia", Volume III, Proceedings, 1980 September (Box 91, Folder 957)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific: Supplementary Material (VIII): Workshop on "The Persian Gulf and the Western Economies", Volume I, Drafts of Research Papers Presented, 1981 January (Box 91, Folder 958)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific: Supplementary Material (IX): Workshop on "The Persian Gulf and the Western Economies", Volume II, Drafts of Research Papers Presented, 1981 January (Box 91, Folder 959)
  - Security Conference on Asia and the Pacific: Supplementary Material (X): "Protecting Persian Gulf Oil: U. S. and Alliance Military Policy", by Albert Wohlstetter, 1980 December (Box 91, Folder 960)
  - Seven Springs Farm Center, Inc.: U. S.-U. S. S. R. Relations, 1975-1977, 1979, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 961)
  - Seven Springs Farm Center, Inc.: U. S.-U. S. S. R. Relations: Evaluation, 1976, 1982-1983 (Box 92, Folder 962)
  - (489) – Skotaville Publishers: Mpikayipheli Figlan: Front of File, 1983, 1985, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 963)
  - (489) – Skotaville Publishers: Mpikayipheli Figlan, 1982-1983 (Box 92, Folder 964)
  - (489) – Skotaville Publishers: Mpikayipheli Figlan, 1984-1987 (Box 92, Folder 965)
  - (489) – Skotaville Publishers: Mpikayipheli Figlan: Supplementary Material (I): Catalogues, 1986-1987 (Box 92, Folder 966)
  - (489) – Skotaville Publishers: Mpikayipheli Figlan: Supplementary Material (II): "The Classic", Volume 1, Number 1, 1982; "The Classic", Volume 3, Number 1, 1984, 1982, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 967)
  - (489) – Skotaville Publishers: Mpikayipheli Figlan: Supplementary Material (III): "The Unquestionable Right to Be Free": Essays in Black Theology, edited by Itumeleng J. Mosala and Buti Tlhagale, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 968)
  - (489) – Skotaville Publishers: Mpikayipheli Figlan: Supplementary Material (IV), 1986 (Box 92, Folder 969)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Front of File and Evaluation, 1976-1979, 1981-1983, 1986-1988, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 970)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations, 1976 February-June (Box 93, Folder 971)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations, 1976 July-1977 February (Box 93, Folder 972)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations, 1977 March-1978 August (Box 93, Folder 973)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations, 1978 September-1979 May (Box 93, Folder 974)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations, 1979 June-1982 March (Box 93, Folder 975)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations, 1982 April-1987 (Box 93, Folder 976)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (I): Annual Reports, 1975, 1978, 1979 (Box 93, Folder 977)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (II), 1976-1978 (Box 94, Folder 978)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (III), 1981-1983, no date (Box 94, Folder 979)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (IV): Draft Papers for Conference on "The Peruvian Experiment Reconsidered", 1978 November 2-4 (Box 94, Folder 980)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (V): Draft Papers for Conference on "The Peruvian Experiment Reconsidered", 1978 November 2-4 (Box 94, Folder 981)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (VI): Draft Papers for Conference on "The Peruvian Experiment Reconsidered", 1978 November 2-4 (Box 94, Folder 982)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (VII): Working Papers, Nos. 1-4, 6-8, 1977-1979 (Box 94, Folder 983)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (VIII): Working Papers, Nos. 9-10, 12, 14-18, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 984)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (IX): Working Papers, Nos. 20-25, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 985)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (X): Working Papers, Nos. 26-32, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 986)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XI): Working Papers, Nos. 33-39, 41, 1978-1979 (Box 95, Folder 987)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XII): Working Papers, Nos. 42-47, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 988)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XIII): Working Papers, Nos. 48-51, 53-54, 60, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 989)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XIV): Working Papers, Nos. 61-66, 1979-1980 (Box 95, Folder 990)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XV): Working Papers, Nos. 67-73, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 991)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XVI): Working Papers, Nos. 74-80, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 992)